<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ComponentSpec isProfile="true" CMDVersion="1.2" CMDOriginalVersion="1.2" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://infra.clarin.eu/CMDI/1.x/xsd/cmd-component.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <Header>
        <ID>clarin.eu:cr1:p_1742217570622</ID>
        <Name>BLAM-collection-repository_v1.1</Name>
        <Description>The Basic Language Archive Metadata Collection profile aims to provide a basic metadata profile for language repositories. The profiles cover fundamental domain specific, but project independent, descriptive metadata as well as basic administrative and structural metadata. BLAM Collection Repository focusses on discoverability and human-readable display without a proliferation of data fields and work for the data producer.</Description>
        <Status>production</Status>
        <DerivedFrom>clarin.eu:cr1:p_1721373444015</DerivedFrom>
    </Header>
    <Component name="BLAM-collection-repository_v1.1" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
        <Element name="MDLicense" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
            <Documentation>The MDLicense element contains information about the license under which the metadata is made available.</Documentation>
            <AttributeList>
                <Attribute name="URI" ValueScheme="anyURI" Required="true">
                    <Documentation>The URI of the license.</Documentation>
                    <AutoValue></AutoValue>
                </Attribute>
            </AttributeList>
        </Element>
        <Component name="CollectionGeneralInfo" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
            <Documentation>CollectionGeneralInfo contains general descriptive metadata about the collection.</Documentation>
            <Element name="CollectionID" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q420330" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionID element contains an identifier that consistently and uniquely identifies the collection described in the particular metadata token. The identifier should be generated by the repository during the initialization process.</Documentation>
                <AttributeList>
                    <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                        <Documentation>The IdentifierType attribute determines the identifier type used. Recommended practice is to have a DOI and a Handle for each collection.</Documentation>
                        <ValueScheme>
                            <Vocabulary>
                                <enumeration>
                                    <item>DOI</item>
                                    <item>Handle</item>
                                    <item>URN</item>
                                    <item>Other</item>
                                </enumeration>
                            </Vocabulary>
                        </ValueScheme>
                    </Attribute>
                </AttributeList>
            </Element>
            <Element name="CollectionVersion" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>CollectionVersion contains the version number of the collection. </Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Element name="CollectionDisplayTitle" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2545_d873f2ab-2a2f-29d6-a9ab-260cde57f227" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionDisplayTitle element provides a human readable name of the collection. It should contain a meaningful and recognisable title for the collection. The content of the CollectionDisplayTitle element will be used as the human readable identifier in interfaces. Data producers can provide CollectionDisplayTitle values for multiple interface languages. This field will be used as the human readable identifier for the collection in citation and interfaces.</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Element name="CollectionDescription" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2520_9eeedfb4-47d3-ddee-cfcb-99ac634bf1db" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionDescription element provides a human readable description of the collection. It should contain a description of the content of the collection. The content of the CollectionDescription element will be used as the human readable description in interfaces. Its content can be queried by repositories for free-text metadata search.</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Component name="CollectionKeywords" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>CollectionKeywords should be used to describe the content and nature of data to enhance the discoverability and facilitate finer granularity for searches and browsing of the data.</Documentation>
                <Element name="CollectionKeyword" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q658349" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>CollectionKeyword should contain a single keyword or a keyphrase and should be used to describe the content and nature of data to enhance the discoverability and facilitate finer granularity for searches and browsing of the data.</Documentation>
                </Element>
            </Component>
            <Component name="CollectionObjectLanguages" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>CollectionObjectLanguages contains information about the language or languages that are the object of the resource.</Documentation>
                <Component name="CollectionObjectLanguage" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                    <Documentation>CollectionObjectLanguage contains information about the language that is the object of the resource.</Documentation>
                    <Element name="ObjectLanguageDisplayName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q3109261" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageDisplayName element contains the name of the object language in the version recommended by the data producer. Repositories should treat the name provided by this element as the primary language name when displaying the metadata in relation to this particular data set. The repository may use alternative names provided by services such as Glottolog or Ethnologue to improve discoverability and to enhance browsing and search experience. The repository may also translate the name into other languages if no language name is given for a particular interface language. </Documentation>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="ObjectLanguageName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q3109261" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageName element contains the name of the object language in the version as provided by services such as Glottolog or Ethnologue.</Documentation>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="ObjectLanguageISO639-3Code" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2092812" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageISO639-3 element contains an ISO 639-3 language code for the object language.</Documentation>
                        <ValueScheme>
                            <pattern>[a-z]{3}</pattern>
                        </ValueScheme>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="ObjectLanguageGlottologCode" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageGlottologCode element contains the Glottolog code for the object language as provided by glottolog.org.</Documentation>
                        <ValueScheme>
                            <pattern>[a-z]{4}[0-9]{4}</pattern>
                        </ValueScheme>
                    </Element>
                    <Component name="ObjectLanguageAlternativeNames" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageAlternativeNames component contains elements with alternative names for the object language as provided by services such as Glottolog or Ethnologue.</Documentation>
                        <Element name="ObjectLanguageAlternativeName" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageAlternativeName element contains an alternative name of the object language as provided by services such as Glottolog or Ethnologue.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                    </Component>
                    <Component name="ObjectLanguageTaxonomy" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageTaxonomy component contains elements with the name of the language family and sub-families or sub-groups the object language belongs to. The values are taken from Glottolog and given in the version as provided by this service. </Documentation>
                        <Element name="ObjectLanguageLanguageFamily" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q3109261" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The ObjectLanguageLanguageFamily element contains the name of the language family and sub-families or sub-groups the object language belongs to. The values are taken from Glottolog and given in the version as provided by this service. </Documentation>
                        </Element>
                    </Component>
                </Component>
            </Component>
            <Component name="CollectionLocation" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>CollectionLocation contains information about the most relevant or salient location in relation to the data contained in the collection. The default location would be the main location of recording. However, any other location viewed as most relevant to the data can be set as the CollectionLocation. The information provided in the component is intended for discoverability and display purposes. Detailed documentation of geographic information should be outsourced into an additional metadata file.</Documentation>
                <Element name="CollectionGeoLocation" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q104224919" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionGeoLocation element contains a geographical coordinates for a location point in the form “LATITUDE,LONGITUDE” as decimal degrees (e.g. 50.926735,6.930392 or -36.427925,150.076214)</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionLocationName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q7884789" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionLocationName element contains the name of a location in the version recommended by the data producer. Repositories should treat the name provided by this element as the primary location name when displaying the metadata in relation to this particular data set.The repository may use alternative names provided by services such as GeoNames to improve discoverability and to enhance the browsing and search experience.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionLocationFacet" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q7884789" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionLocationFacet element contains the name of a location provided by services such as GeoNames. This name is used to improve discoverability and to enhance the browsing and search experience. GeoNames field: “name” (or “toponymName”).</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionRegionName" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2533_fa6e1812-e29b-3cf6-e15a-50aa34b9be68" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionRegionName element optionally contains the name of an administrative subdivision such as state, province, or any other politically salient unit in the version recommended by the data producer. The data producer can decided which level of subdivision is relevant and will improve discoverability. Repositories should treat the name provided by this element as the primary location name when displaying the metadata in relation to this particular data set (e.g. collection or collection). The repository may use alternative names provided by services such as GeoNames to improve discoverability and to enhance browsing and search experience.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionRegionFacet" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2533_fa6e1812-e29b-3cf6-e15a-50aa34b9be68" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionRegionFacet element contains the name of an administrative subdivision provided by services such as GeoNames to improve discoverability and to enhance browsing and search experience. GeoNames field: “adminName1” </Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionCountryName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q6256" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionCountryName element contains the name of the country to which the location belongs in the version recommended by the data producer. Repositories should treat the name provided by this element as the primary country name when displaying the metadata in relation to this particular data set (e.g. collection or collection). The repository may use alternative names provided by services such as GeoNames to improve discoverability and to enhance browsing and search experience.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionCountryFacet" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q6256" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionCountryFacet element contains the name of the country as provided by services such as GeoNames to improve discoverability and to enhance browsing and search experience. GeoNames field: “countryName”</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="CollectionCountryCode" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q906278" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The CountryCode element contains the ISO 3166-1 alpha 2 code of the country of the location as provided by services such as GeoNames GeoNames field: countryCode</Documentation>
                    <ValueScheme>
                        <pattern>[A-Z]{2}</pattern>
                    </ValueScheme>
                </Element>
            </Component>
        </Component>
        <Component name="CollectionPublicationInfo" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
            <Documentation>The CollectionPublicationInfo component contains metadata pertaining the publication of the resource. The information provided in this component is used in the interface of the repository and in particular to generate bibliographical references to the resource.</Documentation>
            <Element name="CollectionPublicationYear" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/P577" ValueScheme="gYear" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>CollectionPublicationYear contains the year of publication in the form YYYY conforming to ISO 8601. The default value is the ingest date into the repository unless an embargo has been set for the resource. In that case, the end year of the embargo is taken as the year of publication. For legacy data, the  value of CollectionPublicationDate can be set to a point before the ingest. The value of this field should be used to generate a bibliographical citation reference for the resource.</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Element name="CollectionDataProvider" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-6134_72c22724-2615-fd70-2eff-8cd3cb59e91d" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>CollectionDataProvider contain the name of the data providing entity. The default value would be the name of the repository or its holding institution. The value of this field can be used to generate a bibliographical citation reference for the resource.</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Component name="CollectionCreators" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionCreator component contains information about the creator or creators of the resource. CollectionCreators are treated as creators of the resource and thus similar to authors in respect to quotation, references, and metadata display. Other individuals involved in the production or processing of the resource should be added as CollectionContributors.</Documentation>
                <Component name="CollectionCreator" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionCreator component contains information about the creator of the resource.</Documentation>
                    <AttributeList>
                        <Attribute name="Order" ValueScheme="int">
                            <Documentation>The Order attribute indicates the order in which the creators should be displayed.</Documentation>
                        </Attribute>
                    </AttributeList>
                    <Element name="CreatorNameIdentifier" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                        <Documentation>The CreatorNameIdentifier contains an URI that uniquely identifies the creator according to an established scheme. ORCID and INSI are considered best practices. An email address in the form of an mailto URI is a fallback.</Documentation>
                        <AttributeList>
                            <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                                <Documentation>ORCID and ISNI are considered best practices. An email address in the form of an mailto URI is a fallback.</Documentation>
                                <ValueScheme>
                                    <Vocabulary>
                                        <enumeration>
                                            <item>ORCID</item>
                                            <item>ISNI</item>
                                            <item>Email</item>
                                            <item>Other</item>
                                        </enumeration>
                                    </Vocabulary>
                                </ValueScheme>
                            </Attribute>
                        </AttributeList>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="CreatorAffiliation" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                        <Documentation>The CreatorAffiliation contains the organisational or institutional affiliation of the creator as provided by the depositor.</Documentation>
                    </Element>
                    <Component name="CreatorName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2500638" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The CreatorName component contains the name of the creator. The value of this field can be used to generate a bibliographical citation reference for the resource. This usage should guide the formatting.</Documentation>
                        <Element name="CreatorFamilyName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2500638" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The CreatorFamilyName element contains the part of the name of the creator that should be treated as the family name when generating a citation for the resource. This usage should guide the decision which part belongs into this field. If the name of a person consist of only one part, it should go here.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                        <Element name="CreatorGivenName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q2500638" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The CreatorGivenName element contains the part of the name of the creator that should be treated as the given name when generating a citation for the resource. This usage should guide the decision.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                    </Component>
                </Component>
            </Component>
            <Component name="CollectionContributors" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionContributors component contains information about contributors to the resource. CollectionContributors are not treated as authors in respect to quotation, references, and metadata display.</Documentation>
                <Component name="CollectionContributor" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionContributor component contains information about a contributor to the resource.</Documentation>
                    <Element name="ContributorNameIdentifier" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                        <Documentation>The ContributorNameIdentifier contains an URI that uniquely identifies the contributor according to an established scheme. ORCID and INSI are considered best practices. An email address in the form of an mailto URI is a fallback.</Documentation>
                        <AttributeList>
                            <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                                <Documentation>ORCID and ISNI are considered best practices. An email address in the form of an mailto URI is a fallback.</Documentation>
                                <ValueScheme>
                                    <Vocabulary>
                                        <enumeration>
                                            <item>ORCID</item>
                                            <item AppInfo="">ISNI</item>
                                            <item>Email</item>
                                            <item>Other</item>
                                        </enumeration>
                                    </Vocabulary>
                                </ValueScheme>
                            </Attribute>
                        </AttributeList>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="ContributorAffiliation" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                        <Documentation>The ContributorAffiliation contains the organisational or institutional affiliation of the contributor as provided by the depositor.</Documentation>
                    </Element>
                    <Element name="ContributorRole" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                        <Documentation>The ContributorRole contains the organisational or institutional affiliation of the contributor as provided by the depositor.</Documentation>
                    </Element>
                    <Component name="ContributorName" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                        <Documentation>The ContributorName component contains the name of the creator. The value of this field may be used to generate a bibliographical citation reference for the resource. This usage should guide the formatting.</Documentation>
                        <Element name="ContributorFamilyName" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The ContributorFamilyName element contains the part of the name of the creator that should be treated as the family name when generating a citation for the resource. This usage should guide the decision. If the name of a person consist of only one part, it should go here.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                        <Element name="ContributorGivenName" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The CreatorGivenName element contains the part of the name of the contributor that should be treated as the given name when generating a citation for the resource. This usage should guide the decision.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                    </Component>
                </Component>
            </Component>
        </Component>
        <Component name="ProjectInfo" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
            <Documentation>ProjectInfo contains descriptive information about the project or the projects relating to the resource.</Documentation>
            <Component name="Project" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                <Documentation>Project contains descriptive information about the project relating to collection data.</Documentation>
                <Element name="ProjectDisplayName" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2536_13fc5f10-c14a-1f64-a669-32736f6d3ef5" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The ProjectDisplayName element provides a human readable name of the project. The preferred form is the abbreviation by which the project is generally known. The long form is best placed in the project description.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="ProjectDescription" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The ProjectDescription element provides a human readable description of the project including full project name. It should contain a description of the project’s objective or activity. The content of the ProjectDescription element will be used as the human readable description in interfaces. Its content can be queried by repositories for free-text metadata search. Data producers can provide ProjectDescription values for multiple interface languages.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Component name="FunderInfos" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The FunderInfos component contains information about the funding organisation or organisations associated with this resource.</Documentation>
                    <Component name="FunderInfo" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                        <Documentation>The FunderInfo component contains information about the funding organisation associated with this resource.</Documentation>
                        <Element name="FunderName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/P8324" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The FunderName element provides the name of the funding organisation. The preferred form is the abbreviation by with the funding agency is generally known.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                        <Element name="FunderIdentifier" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1">
                            <Documentation>The FunderIdentifier contains an URI that uniquely identifies the funding body according to an established scheme.</Documentation>
                            <AttributeList>
                                <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                                    <Documentation>The IdentifierType attribute determines the identifier type used.</Documentation>
                                    <ValueScheme>
                                        <Vocabulary>
                                            <enumeration>
                                                <item>CrossrefFunder</item>
                                                <item>ISNI</item>
                                                <item>GRID</item>
                                                <item>Other</item>
                                            </enumeration>
                                        </Vocabulary>
                                    </ValueScheme>
                                </Attribute>
                            </AttributeList>
                        </Element>
                        <Element name="GrantIdentifier" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>GrantIdentifier contains an element that uniquely identifies the grant according to an established scheme. Best Practice: funding body specific identifier such as NSF grant number or BMBF Förderkennzeichen.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                        <Element name="GrantURI" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                            <Documentation>The GrantURI contains an URI that uniquely identifies the grant and funding body according to an established scheme.</Documentation>
                        </Element>
                    </Component>
                </Component>
            </Component>
        </Component>
        <Component name="CollectionAdministrativeInfo" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
            <Documentation>CollectionAdministrativeInfo contains administrative metadata that will be publicly communicated, especially in regard to metacatalogues and user interfaces.</Documentation>
            <Element name="CollectionIsIdenticalTo" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionIsIdenticalTo element contains an URI that uniquely identifies an identical resource. This element should only be used if it can be ascertained that the identified resource and the current resource will remain identical; else CollectionIsDerivationOf should be used. The CollectionIsIdenticalTo relationship is based on the `hasEquivalent` relationship of the Fedora Relationship Ontology (http://www.fedora.info/definitions/1/0/fedora-relsext-ontology.rdfs).</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Element name="CollectionIsDerivationOf" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionIsDerivationOf element contains an URI that uniquely identifies the resource from which the current resource is derived. The CollectionIsDerivationOf relationship is based on the `isDerivationOf` relationship of the Fedora Relationship Ontology (http://www.fedora.info/definitions/1/0/fedora-relsext-ontology.rdfs).</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Element name="Access" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-2453_1f0c3ea5-7966-ae11-d3c6-448424d4e6e8" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>This element specifies the terms of availability of the resource in plain words. The  technical implementation of these terms depends on the repository.</Documentation>
                <ValueScheme>
                    <Vocabulary>
                        <enumeration>
                            <item>open</item>
                            <item>registration required</item>
                            <item>request required</item>
                        </enumeration>
                    </Vocabulary>
                </ValueScheme>
            </Element>
            <Element name="AvailabilityDate" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-6711_135e104e-9f0e-265a-0e6e-4e2325c8751e" ValueScheme="date" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                <Documentation>The AvailabilityDate element contains the date at which the bundle became or will become available. The date must be provided conforming to ISO 8601 in the form YYYY-MM-DD.</Documentation>
            </Element>
            <Component name="License" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                <Documentation>The License component contains information about the license under which the resource is available.</Documentation>
                <Element name="LicenseName" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q79719" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The LicenseName element should provide the complete human readable name of a license and include version information if applicable.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="LicenseIdentifier" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-6586_2c79d86a-5a75-0890-d407-7d9cb86b9beb" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The LicenseIdentifier provides a URI for the license.</Documentation>
                </Element>
            </Component>
            <Component name="RightsHolder" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                <Documentation>The RightsHolder component contains information about the individual or institution owning or managing the rights in regard to the resource.</Documentation>
                <Element name="RightsHolderName" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-6709_cb3572ed-ffd3-04f1-c145-b9c1f26bfc82" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                    <Documentation>The RightsHolderName contains the name of the individual or institution owning or managing the rights over the resource.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="RightsHolderIdentifier" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The RightsHolderIdentifier contains a URI that uniquely identifies the rights holder. In the case of an individual, this should be achieved by using an established scheme. Best Practice: ORCID, ISNI If an individual cannot be referenced by an identifier an email address should be given (in the form of a mailto URI).</Documentation>
                    <AttributeList>
                        <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                            <Documentation>ORCID and ISNI are considered best practices. An email address in the form of a mailto URI is the recommended fallback.</Documentation>
                            <ValueScheme>
                                <Vocabulary>
                                    <enumeration>
                                        <item>ORCID</item>
                                        <item>ISNI</item>
                                        <item AppInfo="">Email</item>
                                        <item>Other</item>
                                    </enumeration>
                                </Vocabulary>
                            </ValueScheme>
                        </Attribute>
                    </AttributeList>
                </Element>
            </Component>
        </Component>
        <Component name="CollectionStructuralInfo" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
            <Documentation>CollectionStructuralInfo contains structural metadata that describes the internal structure of the collection.</Documentation>
            <Component name="CollectionAdditionalMetadataFile" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="unbounded">
                <Documentation>The CollectionAdditionalMetadataFile component contains metadata about additional metadata files contained in the collection.</Documentation>
                <Element name="FileName" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The FileName element contains the name of the file as provided by the depositor.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="FilePID" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The FileID element contains a PID that uniquely identifies the file described by this component.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="MimeType" ConceptLink="http://www.wikidata.org/entity/Q1667978" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>Specification of the mime-type of the resource.</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="IsMetadataFor" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The IsMetadataFor element contains a PID that uniquely identifies the file described by the file described in this component. The IsMetadataFor relationship is based on the `isMetadataFor` relationship of the Fedora Relationship Ontology (http://www.fedora.info/definitions/1/0/fedora-relsext-ontology.rdfs).</Documentation>
                </Element>
                <Element name="FileDescription" ValueScheme="string" CardinalityMin="0" CardinalityMax="1" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The FileDescription contains a human readable, file specific description. This element should be used to provide file specific that cannot be added to the collection description. Any information applicable to the whole collection should be added to the CollectionDescription element.</Documentation>
                </Element>
            </Component>
            <Component name="CollectionMembers" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="1">
                <Documentation>The CollectionMembers component contains elements referencing the bundles of the collection.</Documentation>
                <Element name="CollectionHasCollectionMember" ConceptLink="http://hdl.handle.net/11459/CCR_C-6570_90018537-4ab9-0cfe-c878-257b9b311993" ValueScheme="anyURI" CardinalityMin="1" CardinalityMax="unbounded" cue:DisplayPriority="1" xmlns:cue="http://www.clarin.eu/cmd/cues/1">
                    <Documentation>The CollectionHasCollectionMember element contains references to a bundle contained in the collection. The CollectionHasCollectionMember relationship is based on the `hasCollectionMember` relationship of the Fedora Relationship Ontology (http://www.fedora.info/definitions/1/0/fedora-relsext-ontology.rdfs).</Documentation>
                    <AttributeList>
                        <Attribute name="IdentifierType" Required="true">
                            <Documentation>The IdentifierType attribute determines the identifier type used.</Documentation>
                            <ValueScheme>
                                <Vocabulary>
                                    <enumeration>
                                        <item>DOI</item>
                                        <item>Handle</item>
                                    </enumeration>
                                </Vocabulary>
                            </ValueScheme>
                        </Attribute>
                    </AttributeList>
                </Element>
            </Component>
        </Component>
    </Component>
</ComponentSpec>
